A Guide to the David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, RG 44 FA253
Rockefeller Archive Center
- David Rockefeller General Files (Room 5600), 1992-1996, 44; 54.6 Cubic Feet 42 standard record storage boxes.
  - Education, 1992-1996; 11
    - Colleges - United Negro College Fund (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - University of the Andes Foundation, Inc. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Colleges - University of Cape Town Fund (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - University of Chicago (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - University of London (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - University of London - London School of Economics and Political Science (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - University of Miami, Coral Gables, FL (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - University of Notre Dame (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - University of the West Indies (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Service Students - A-Z (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Foundations - A-Z (Box 57, Folder 1-4)
    - Foundations - Winston Churchill Foundation of the United States (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Foundations - George C. Marshall Foundation (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Foundations - Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Foundations - Margaret Thatcher Foundation (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Historical Societies - A-Z (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Housing - A-Z (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Housing - International House, New York City (Box 58, Folder 5-6)
    - Radio-TV - A-Z (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Radio-TV - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Radio-TV - Varied Directions International (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Radio-TV - WETA (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Schools - A-C (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Schools - D-Z (Box 60, Folder 1-4)
    - Schools - American Academy in Rome (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Schools - American Farm School in Greece (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Schools - The Children's Storefront (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Schools - Outward Bound, USA (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Waynflete School, Portland, ME (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Energy, 1992-1996; 12
    - Energy - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - F-I, 1992-1996; 13
    - F - Miscellaneous - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Finances - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - G - Miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Geriatrics - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - H - Miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Hispanic Affairs - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Hispanic Affairs - Casita Maria, Inc. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Historic Hudson Valley - A-Z (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Historic Hudson Valley- Fundraising - A-Z (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Horticulture - A-Z (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - IBEC (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - International Relations, 1992-1996; 14
    - International Relations - A-F (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - International Relations - G-T (Box 63, Folder 1-5)
    - International Relations - U-Z (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Africa - A-Z (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - American Council on Germany (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Americanism (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Argentina (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Asia - A-Z (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Asia - Asia Foundation (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Asia - Asia Society (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Contributions (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Burma (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - China - A-Z (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - China - America-China Society (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - China - China Institute in America (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - CIVICUS - World Alliance for Citizen Participation (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - CIVICUS Files - Peter Johnson (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - CIVICUS Files - Peter Johnson - Possible Op-Ed piece by David Rockefeller (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - CIVICUS - Mexico City, 1995 January (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Coalition for International Security (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Council for the United States and Italy (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Eisenhower World Affairs Institute (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Forum for International Policy (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - France - A-Z (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - France - French-American Foundation (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Institute for East West Studies (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - International Rescue Committee (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Islam and the West (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Israel - A-Z (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Italy - A-Z (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Japan - A-Z (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Japan - Japan Society - A-Z (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Japan - The Japan Foundation (Box 68, Folder 6-7)
    - Bruno Kreisky Forum for International Dialogue (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Mexico - A-M (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Mexico - N-Z (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Pakistan - A-Z (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Poland (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Poland - Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Russia - A-Z (Box 69, Folder 7-8)
    - Russia - Dartmouth Conference (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Russia - Russian American Banking (Bankers) Forum (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
    - South Africa - A-Z (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - South Africa - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program, Inc. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Spanish Institute (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Thailand - A-Z (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Thailand - National Institute of Development Administration (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Vietnam - A-Z (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Aid - A-Z (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Aid - Citizens Network for Foreign Affairs (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Aid - Overseas Development Council (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid - Resources Development Foundation (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - Synergos Institute (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - A-Z (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - A-Z (Box 72, Folder 4-5)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions (Box 72, Folder 6-7)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Fundraising (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - International Advisory Board (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Nelson and David Rockefeller Chair in Inter-American Studies (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - A-Z (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Trips - Asia, 1993 October (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Trips - South Africa, 1994 October (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - Foreign Policy Association (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
    - Foreign Policy - National Committee on American Foreign Policy, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Pan American - A-Z (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - A-Z (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Contributions (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Chairman's International Advisory Council (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Forum of the Americas - A-Z (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Presidential Summit, Santa Cruz, Bolivia (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Center for Inter-American Relations (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Council of the Americas - A-Z (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Council of the Americas - Summit of the Americas - A-Z (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Washington Conference, 1994 May 2-3 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Grupo Esquel (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Peace - A-Z (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Peace - Bilderberg Conference-Meetings (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Peace - Bilderberg Meetings - Contributions (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Peace - Business Executives for National Security (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Peace - International Peace Academy (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - United Nations (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - A-Z (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
    - United Nations - Business Council of the United Nations (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - United Nations - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - United Nations - 50th Anniversary (Box 76, Folder 8, Box 77, Folder 1-2)
    - United Nations - High Commissioner's Office for Refugees (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - United Nations Conference on Environment and Development (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Executive Council on Diplomacy (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Agency for International Development (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - Agency for International Development - International Executive Service Corps (Box 77, Folder 7, Box 78, Folder 1-5)
    - United States Government - Agency for International Development - International Executive Service Corps - A-Z (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Agency for International Development - International Executive Service Corps - Meetings (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - Department of State - A-Z (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of State - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - J-M, 1992-1996; 15
    - J - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - K - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - L - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - M - Miscellaneous - A-Z (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Medicine, 1992-1996; 16
    - Medicine - A-B (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Medicine - C-Z (Box 80, Folder 1-5)
    - American Cancer Society (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - American Foundation for Aids Research (AmFAR) (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Arthritis Foundation (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Beckman Laser Institute & Medical Clinic (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Cancer Care, Inc. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Deafness Research Foundation (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - The Jackson Laboratory, Bar Harbor, Maine (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - New York Blood Center (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - VZV Research Foundation, Inc. (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Alcoholism - A-Z (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - A-Z (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
    - Hospitals - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Hospital for Special Surgery, New York, NY (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Hospitals - Society of the New York Hospital - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health - A-Z (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Narcotics - A-Z (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Narcotics - The Mentor Foundation (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Narcotics - Phoenix House (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - N-P, 1992-1996; 17
    - N, O, P - Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Philanthropy, 1992-1996; 18
    - Philanthropic Collaborative (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Philanthropy - A-Z (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Politics, 1992-1996; 19
    - Politics - A-Z (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Lamar Alexander - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Patrick J. Buchanan - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Robert Dole - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate, Texas (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Steve Forbes - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Phil Gramm - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Jack Kemp - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Richard Lugar - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Contributions (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous - 1996 Presidential Candidates, GOP (Relevant Material) (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Millard, Charles (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - New York Republican County Committee (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Republican National Committee and Republican National Finance Committee Ripon Society (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Arlen Specter - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Pete Wilson - 1996 Republican Presidential Candidate (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Population, 1992-1996; 20
    - Population - A-Z (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of New York City (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Population Council (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Population - Abortion - A-Z (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Q-R, 1992-1996; 21
    - R - Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Race Relations, 1992-1996; 22
    - Race Relations - A-Z (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate, 1992-1996; 23
    - Real Estate - A-Z (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - The Enterprise Foundation (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Greenrock - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit - A-Z (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico Hills - Kykuit- Works of Art (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Pocantico Hills - The Playhouse - A-Z (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Group - Rockefeller Center Properties, Inc. (Box 98, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2042.
    - Rockefeller Group - A-Z (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Group - Rockefeller Center (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Center - Christmas Tree (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Religion, 1992-1996; 24
    - Religion - A-Z (Box 87, Folder 4-6)
    - The American Jewish Committee (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Appeal of Conscience Foundation (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - World Council of Churches (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Churches - A-Z (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
    - Churches - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Churches - Frauenkirche, Dresden, Germany (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Churches - Riverside Church, New York, NY (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Churches - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Missions - A-Z (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1992-1996; 25
    - Rockefeller family - A-Z (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Family - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corporation - A-Z (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Family - Awards - A-Z (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Family - Awards - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Family - Abby R. Mauze Charitable Trust - A-Z (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Family - Trusts - A-Z (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - A (Box 89, Folder 8-9)
    - Rockefeller, David - B-C (Box 90, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - D-Fo (Box 91, Folder 1-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Fp-H (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - I-L (Box 93, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - L-N (Box 94, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - O-Re (Box 95, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Rf-S (Box 96, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - T-Z (Box 97, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks-Statements - A-Z (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks-Statements - Economic Club of New York (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks-Statements - Japan Society (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Alessandro, Kent and Mrs. (Marisa) (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Ali, Syed Amjad (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Andreotti, Giulio (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Armenise, Giovanni Auletta (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Armstrong, Richard W. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - A-Z (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - Asahi, Shimbun (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - Lideres Mexicanos (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - Town and Country (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Astor, Mrs. W. Vincent (Brooke) (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Autographs-Photographs - A-Z (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - A-Z (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - French-American Foundation (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - Japanese Chamber of Commerce and Industry of New York, Inc. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - National Committee on United States China Relations (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - Preservation League of New York State (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - World Monuments Fund (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Bagarotti, Mrs. Giovanni (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Beetles - A-Z (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Benson-Wright, Penelope (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Binnewies, Robert O. and Mrs. (Midge) (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Book (Memoirs) (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Butcher, Willard C. (Bill) and Mrs. Carol (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - Champion, Robert C. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Cisneros R., Gustavo A. and Mrs. (Patricia Phelps) (Patty) (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Crown Prince Hassan Bin Talal (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Davis, Shelby Cullom and Mrs. (Kathryn) de Montbrial, Thierry (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - de Montbrial, Thierry (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Deng, Dr. Francis (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - de Rosen, Leon (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners-Luncheons-Receptions - Synergos Institute (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Drouhin, Robert J. and Mrs. (Françoise) (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - Edmundson, Kathryn (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Edwards, Agustin E. (Doonie) and Mrs. (Malu) (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller, David - Espinosa Yglesias, Angeles (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller, David - Frisby, Owen V. (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller, David - Giving Program Book Prepared by Trix Smalley, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Gyllenhammar, Pehr G. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Hauschka, Theodore and Mrs. (Elsa) (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Hewitt, William A. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Holmes, Christian R., IV (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Investments - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitation to Speak - A-Z (Box 103, Folder 8-9)
    - Rockefeller, David - King Bhumibol Adulyadej and Queen Sirikit (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Knight, Ridgeway (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Kuruvilla, E.J. (Sonny) and Mrs. (Indira) (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Levingston, Bruce (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Loans (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Madero, Enrique Bracho (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Madero Bracho, Antonio (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Martinez de Hoz, Dr. Jose (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - McCrary, John Reagan (TEX) (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Menem, Carlos Saul (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - Moreira Salles, Dr. Walther and Mrs. (Lucia) (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Morita, Akio (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller, David - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller, David - Pahlavi, Farah (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller, David - Pappalardo, Conrado (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller, David - Pappenheimer, Dr. John R. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller, David - Personal Services - A-Z (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller, David - Peterson, Peter G. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - A-Z (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Maine (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Seal Harbor - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Garden - A-Z (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Purchases - A-Z (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Reed, Joseph V., Jr. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Robinson, Roger W., Jr. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Rose, Frederick P. (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Stremlau, John (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Swanzey, Thomas (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - A-Z (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Asia (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - Middle East, 1994 November (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - South Africa, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips - West Coast and Houston, 1996 March (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trusts - A-Z (Box 119, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members.
    - Rockefeller, David - Wang, Jialin (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, David - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. David (Margaret McGrath "Peggy") - A-Z (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. David (Margaret McGrath "Peggy") - Death (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. David (Margaret McGrath "Peggy") - Death - Guest Books, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 3-5, Box 118, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller Family - A-Z (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, John D. (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D. Jr. (Abby Aldrich) (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Family - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D. Jr. (Abby Aldrich) - Kert, Bernice (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., 3rd - Death Condolences - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - Winrock International (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1992-1996; 26
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Contributions (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Meetings (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Family Office, 1992-1996; 27
    - Philanthropy (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller and Company - A-Z (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - A-Z (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services - Chairmanship (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1992-1996; 28
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller University, 1992-1996; 29
    - Rockefeller University - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Contributions (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - A-Z (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Meetings, 1993-1995 (Box 109, Folder 4-5)
  - S, 1992-1996; 30
    - S - Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Science - A-Z (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Science - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Science - Society of Scientific Exploration (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Seal Harbor Organization - A-Z (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - T-W, 1992-1996; 31
    - T - Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - U-V - Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Westchester Organizations - A-Z (Box 114, Folder 8)